https://www.greatbeanbags.com/privacy-policy

Toggle Nav
Free Shipping & delivered next working day!
Maternity Bean Bags
Accessories Bean Bag RefillsBean Bag CoversFur ThrowsGift CardsBean Bag NettingBean Bag CushionsBean Bag RefillsBean Bag CoversFur ThrowsGift CardsBean Bag NettingBean Bag CushionsPets Dog Bean BagsCat Bean BagsDog Bean BagsCat Bean BagsIndustry Branded & Event Bean BagsTrade Bean BagsSchool Bean BagsMedical Bean BagsBranded & Event Bean BagsTrade Bean BagsSchool Bean BagsMedical Bean BagsAccount Sign InRegisterMy AccountSign OutContact UsDelivery InformationReturns & ExchangesFabric SamplesSizing ChartSign InRegisterMy AccountSign OutContact UsDelivery InformationReturns & ExchangesFabric SamplesSizing Chart
My Basket
Account
Search
Search
Popular Searches
Foam bean ba
(257)
faux fur
(70)
Outdoor bean bags
(1)
outdoor
(3)
Search
Privacy Policy
GreatBeanBags is a trading name of Precision Stitching Ltd.
The privacy policy explains how we use any personal information we collect about you when you use this website.
What information do we collect about you?
How will we use the information about you?
Access to your information, correction and removal
Cookies
Other websites
Changes to our privacy policy
How to contact us
What information do we collect about you?
We collect information about you when you register with us or place an order for products or services. This information includes your:
Name
Postal address(es)
Telephone number(s)
Email address(es)
If you have a registered account on the website, the following information is collected and stored as you use the website and place orders:
Details of your previous orders
Details of intended purchases (e.g. shopping basket contents, wishlist)
The IP address of the network connection used when placing an order
We do not collect or store any of your personal information if you do not register with us or place an order.
Back to top
How will we use the information about you?
We collect information about you to enable us to:
Process your order
Manage your account
Allow you to recall previous orders and use your saved personal information when making an order (to speed things up for you!).
When making an order with us, your personal information is shared with the following:
Payment processors (PayPal / Amazon Pay / DivideBuy) - Your information is shared to enable these companies to process your payment securely and for fraud prevention reasons. Your information is only shared with with these companies if you choose to use their service to pay for your order.
Delivery companies - If you order includes physical items, your address information is shared with our delivery partners to enable us to deliver your order.
TrustPilot (https://www.trustpilot.com) - We provide your name, email address and details of your purchase to our reviews partner once you place an order with us. They will then send you an email to ask if you would like to review our service and products.
We will not share your personal information with any other external companies without your additional, prior consent.
Back to top
Access to your information, correction and removal
You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please contact us.
If you believe that any information that we hold about you is incorrect, please contact us and, where appropriate, we will work with you to correct the information.
You also have the right to request that we destroy all of the information that we hold about you (your "right to be forgotten"). Again, please contact us if you’d like to us to do this and we’ll be happy to oblige.
Back to top
Cookies
Cookies are small data files that allow a website to collect and store a range of data on your desktop computer, laptop or mobile device. Cookies help us to provide important features and functionality on our website.
We use cookies on this website to:
Store your shopping basket contents when browsing the website
Remember how you like to view the website (how you like the categories to be sorted, for example)
We also use cookies which collect anonymous data about how our customers use our website. This includes which pages are viewed, which products are purchased and how you found our website. This allows us to monitor and improve our website, as well as providing us with information about how well our advertising is working.
The cookies used to collect this anonymous data are provided by:
Google - https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en-GB
Facebook - https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation
For further information about cookies, please visit http://www.aboutcookies.org.uk.
You can set your browser not to accept cookies, and the above website includes instructions of how to remove cookies from your browser. Please note that setting your browser not to accept cookies, or removing cookies whilst shopping with us, will negatively affect your shopping experience (for example, not allowing you to add items to your shopping basket).
Back to top
Other websites
Our website contains links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website, so when you visit links to other websites you should read their own privacy policies.
Back to top
Changes to our privacy policy
We keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any updates on this page. This privacy policy was last updated on 8th May 2018.
Back to top
How to contact us
You can contact us using any of the following methods:
Telephone: 0115 9557373
Telephone (outside of the UK): +44 115 9557373
Email: info@greatbeanbags.com
Post:
GreatBeanBags (Precision Stitching Ltd)
